export const Aptitudequestions  = {
    topic: 'Aptitude',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 12,
    perQuestionScore: 5,

  questions: [
    {
      question: 'An exam was conducted and the following was analyzed. 4 men were able to check some exam papers in 8 days working 5 hours regularly. What is the total number of hours taken by 2 men in 20 days to check double the number of exam papers?',
      choices: ['8 hours', '4 hours', '2 hours', '6 hours'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '8 hours',
    },
    {
      question: 'The numbers from 101 to 150 are written as, 101102103104105…146147148149150. What will be the remainder when this total number is divided by 3?',
      choices: ['3', '2', '5', '1'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '2',
    },
    {
      question:
        'There is a tank whose 1/7 th part is filled with fuel. If 22 liters of fuel is poured into the tank, the indicator rises to 1/5 th mark of the tank. So what is the total capacity of the tank?',
      choices: ['359', '285', '455', '385'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '385',
    },
    {
      question: 'There is a town called Metron, where the wheels of the front and rear of vehicles are of different sizes. The measurement unit followed in the town is the meter. The circumference of the front wheel of the car is 133 meters and that of rear wheels is 190 meters. So what is the distance travelled by the cart in meters when the front wheel has done nine more revolutions than the rear wheel? ',
      choices: ['1330', '572', '399', '3990'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '3990',
    },
    {
      question: '30 liters of 78% of a concentrated acid solution is to be prepared. How many litres of 90% concentrated acid needs to be mixed with 75% solution of concentrated acid to get the result? ',
      choices: ['10', '6', '3', '4'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '6',
    },
    {
      question: 'In a class, the number of boys is equal to the number of girls. What was the total number of students if twice the number of boys as girls remain when 12 girls entered out? ',
      choices: ['55', '48', '65', '44'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '48',
    },
    {
      question: 'There is a chocolate factory which distributes chocolates to a class. It supplies chocolates to a class of 50 students for 30 days, keeping in mind that all students get an equal number of chocolates. For the first 10 days, only 20 students were present. How many students be accommodated into the group so that all the chocolates get consumed?',
      choices: ['70', '55', '60', '45'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '45',
    },
    {
      question: "Given, log(0.318) = 0.3364 and log(0.317) = 0.3332, find log(0.319)?",
      choices: ['0.3396', '0.3394', '0.3393', '0.0390'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '0.3396',
    },
    {
      question: "An athletic run at 9 km/hr along a railway track. The track is 240m long and ahead of a train 120m long running at 45km/hr, in the same direction. how much time will the train take to completely cross the athlete?",
      choices: ['3.6 sec', '18 sec', '36 sec', '72 sec'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '36 sec',
    },
    {
      question: "A takes 3 days to complete a work while B takes 2 days. Both of them finish a work and earn Rs. 150. What is A’s share of money?",
      choices: [' Rs. 70', 'Rs. 30', 'Rs. 60 ', 'Rs. 75'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Rs. 60',
    },
    {
      question: "Ram and Shyam salaries are in the ratio of 2:3. If both of there salaries are increased by Rs 4000 each, the new ratio becomes 40:57. What is Shyam’s present salary?",
      choices: [' Rs. 17, 000', 'Rs. 20, 000', 'Rs. 34000', 'Rs. 25, 500'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'Rs. 34000',
    },
    {
      question: "At what rate per cent per annum will the SI on a sum of money be 2/5 of the amount in 10 years?",
      choices: ['6%', '5 2/3 %', '6 2/3 %', '4%'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: '4%',
    },
  ],
}
